{"__cache./api/resource/task/60221/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":60221,"taskName":"Tankless Water Heater - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Tankless Water Heater System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tankless Water Heater Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":264,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"tankless water heater, tankless, water, heater, repair, fix, hot water heater, electric water heater","textMessagingName":"Tankless Water Heater Repair","rolloverLongDesc":"Also called On Demand water heaters, these systems heat your water as you use it without the need of a storage tank. Thus reducing the standby energy loss of a conventional storage tank hot water heater.","rolloverShortDesc":"Energy Efficient - Heats water as you use it","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to repair a tankless water heater. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened tankless water heater repair contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Tankless Water Heater Repair | Fix Hot Water Heater","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":60,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Tankless Water Heater Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tankless Water Heater - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Tankless Water Heater Project","urlName":"Tankless-Water-Heater-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Tankless Water Heater Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"tankless water heater, tankless, hot water heater, electric water heater, repair, fix","emcCategoryOid":-12058,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":5264,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tankless Water Heater Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/60221/":{"taskOID":60221,"originalTaskOID":60221,"setID":5264,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1418,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the nature of the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4208,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":782,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Annual maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4288,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not enough hot water","answerDisplayText":"Not enough hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3510,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Leaking or cracked pipe","answerDisplayText":"Leaking or cracked pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3727,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Making noise","answerDisplayText":"Making noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3087,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hot water fluctuations","answerDisplayText":"Hot water fluctuations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4685,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pilot light is out","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light is out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1137,"questionDisplayText":"Heat Source for Hot Water","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the heat source for the water heater?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4027,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Natural gas","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4939,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Propane","answerDisplayText":"Propane","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5868,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Solar","answerDisplayText":"Solar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1418,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the nature of the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4208,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":782,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Annual maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4288,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not enough hot water","answerDisplayText":"Not enough hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3510,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Leaking or cracked pipe","answerDisplayText":"Leaking or cracked pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3727,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Making noise","answerDisplayText":"Making noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3087,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hot water fluctuations","answerDisplayText":"Hot water fluctuations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4685,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pilot light is out","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light is out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4208,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No hot water","answerDisplayText":"No hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":782,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Annual maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4288,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Not enough hot water","answerDisplayText":"Not enough hot water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3510,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Leaking or cracked pipe","answerDisplayText":"Leaking or cracked pipe","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3727,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Making noise","answerDisplayText":"Making noise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3087,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hot water fluctuations","answerDisplayText":"Hot water fluctuations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4685,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pilot light is out","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light is out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1137,"questionDisplayText":"Heat Source for Hot Water","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the heat source for the water heater?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4027,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Natural gas","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4939,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Propane","answerDisplayText":"Propane","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5868,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Solar","answerDisplayText":"Solar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4027,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Natural gas","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4939,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Propane","answerDisplayText":"Propane","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5868,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Solar","answerDisplayText":"Solar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}